ICC Bank made a big announcement ICC Lombard shares rose by 14%
ICC
Lombard General Insurance shares
saw a tremendous rise on Monday
ICC Lombard General Insurance ICC
Lombard General Insurance shares rose by
14% on Monday to reach Rs 1256.7 on the Bombay Stock Exchange
This rise in the insurance company's shares has
come due to an announcement made by ICC Bank
ICC Lombard shares' 52 week
high
is 1369
ICC Bank
announced to buy 4% stake Actually, this bank has announced its plan related to
increasing 4% stake in ICC Bank
ICC Bank will buy at
least 2.5% of this 4% stake on 9
September 2014
Domestic brokerage house Motilal Oswal
Financial Services has
maintained a buy rating on ICC Bank shares and has
given a target price of Rs 100400
Currently, this is the bank's stake in ICC Lombard Currently,
ICC Bank has a buy rating
in ICC Bank's own general insurance unit ICC Lombard
48.00% stake As per
Reserve Bank of India guidelines, the
bank can either hold less than 30% stake
or increase its stake to
more than 50%
ICC Bank has also
informed the exchange that its board has approved the reappointment
of Sandeep Batra as Executive Director for two more
years